You're next.
Truth or Dare is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Robert Heath.
A group of friends are lured to an isolated cabin by a promise of heavy partying,
only to find themselves in a nightmarish game of truth or dare.
Paul, played by Liam Boyle.
Chris, played by Jack Gordon.
Gemma, played by Florence Hall.
Justin, played by David Oakes.
Eleanor, played by Jennie Jacques.
Felix, played by Tom Kane.
Truth or Dare (released in the United States as Truth or Die) is a 2012 British
psychological horror film directed by Robert Heath and written by Matthew McGuchan.
The film stars David Oakes, Tom Kane, Jennie Jacques, Liam Boyle,
Jack Gordon, Florence Hall and Alexander Vlahos.
It made 2.5 million at the box office  against its budget of 1 million.
The film explores themes of suicide, bullying, revenge, murder, torture.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.